robertpattinsononline.com 2011-05-14

# Privacy Policy • ROBERT PATTINSON ONLINE • Celebrating Two Years Online • Your Source for Robert Pattinson!

Privacy Policy for RobertPattinsonOnline.com

The privacy of our visitors to RobertPattinsonOnline.com is important to us.

At RobertPattinsonOnline.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visitRobertPattinsonOnline.com and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums and comments.

We also use third party advertisements on RobertPattinsonOnline.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Links  
The site does contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy rules or content on the other sites.

Children Under 13  
As part of the Children’s Online Protection Privacy Act, we have the following information on collecting information from children under the age of 13. While our site doesn’t necessarily aim towards children under 13, some children of that age may stumble upon our site. However, before giving out any information, we do ask that you always ask your parent or guardian’s permission.

We may at times ask for your email/name without prior consent from your parents:  
– to allow a one time communication, in which the email will be deleted after that communication.   
– to comply with any law enforcement. to respond to children’s specific requests to participate in activities such as:  
\- contests or sweepstakes  
\- subscription to an online newsletter  
\- voting in polls or otherwise expressing an opinion

When viewing the site, it may be necessary to give us your email/name for polls, contests or to comment on the site, however no contact information (such as email or name) is necessary to simply view the site. As an added caution, we do ask that you do not give out personal information such as name, email, address, telephone number, or any other information such as in the comments or forum. These areas remain open to public viewing. As always, ask your parents/guardian before giving any information out at all.

Parents can review the information that we have collected from their children online, prevent the further use or maintenance of such information, or direct the deletion of their children’s personal information by:

\- emailing us at the email provided: [here](http://www.robertpattinsononline.com/website/contact.php).

We respect the privacy of children, and do not collect any more personal information than reasonably necessary to enable them to participate in the activities we offer at our website. No information will be given to third parties, unless otherwise noted by us where it will be clearly visible. 

We do not share children’s personal information with anyone other than those who provide support for the internal operations of the Website and our agents (e.g., contractors who provide fulfillment services or technical support to the Website).
